<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://perfumeonline.ca/blogs/blogs.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://perfumeonline.ca/blogs/blogs"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://perfumeonline.ca/blogs/blogs.atom"/>
  <title>Perfumeonline.ca - Blogs</title>
  <updated>2018-05-14T11:45:00-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Perfumeonline.ca</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://perfumeonline.ca/blogs/blogs/best-perfumes-for-women</id>
    <published>2018-05-14T11:45:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2018-06-02T04:47:05-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://perfumeonline.ca/blogs/blogs/best-perfumes-for-women"/>
    <title>5 Best Perfumes For Women&apos;s</title>
    <author>
      <name>Perfume Online</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>After researching more than 50 hours and evaluating more than 150 products we picked Lancôme La Vie Est Belle L'Eau EDT as the best perfume for women. It is perfume forest out there and every lady wants to smell nice. Smelling pretty not only makes a lady feel good but also can increase confidence. Find your signature scent from our most trusted best perfumes for women’s list.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<a href="https://perfumeonline.ca/collections/women-s-perfume/products/la-vie-est-belle" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Lancôme La Vie Est Belle L'Eau Eau De Toilette </strong></a>- This is a very lovely perfume for ladies that gives a very romantic scent. This is why is very important for midnight occasions. It delivers a powerful scent that combined with sweet, fresh, spicy and floral notes. The great balance of top, base and mid tops makes this fragrance perfect to wear if you are going out for a romantic evening. However, it is still good to wear if you are working.</li>
</ol>
<ol start="2">
<li>
<a href="https://perfumeonline.ca/products/ysl-opium-black" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Black Opium by Yves Saint Laurent</strong></a> – this popular perfume for women was created in 2014 by acclaimed perfumers Nathalie Lorson and Marie Salamagne. This Is one of best perfumes for women, it has top notes of sweet vanilla and spicy pink pepper. This fragrance feels comfortable yet luxurious. This warm fragrance is good for the winter season for all age groups.</li>
</ol>
<ol start="3">
<li>
<a href="https://perfumeonline.ca/collections/viktor-rolf/products/v-r-flowerbomb" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Viktor &amp; Rolf Flowerbomb</strong></a> - this fragrance has a sweet and flowery smell with hints of musk and patchouli. Great to wear if are going out for any social event or on a romantic evening. This perfume only needs a few sprays on you and it will last on you all day. This fragrance assures you of a feminine and sexy scent that is seductive to man.</li>
</ol>
<ol start="4">
<li>
<a href="https://perfumeonline.ca/collections/shop-under-40/products/viva-la-juicy" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Viva La Juicy by Juicy Couture</strong></a> – this is very unique and intoxicating scent featuring top notes such as mandarin orange, gardenia and wild berries with occasional hints of caramel, sandalwood and amber. This very fun and delightful fragrance for women that keeps you feel well and fresh. You can wear this fragrance wherever or whenever you want but for shorter occasions.</li>
</ol>
<ol start="5">
<li>
<a href="https://perfumeonline.ca/collections/women-s-perfume/products/hypnotic-poison" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Hypnotic Poison by Christian Dior</strong></a> – this scent was created in 1998 by acclaimed perfumer AnnickManardo. this is a warm scent, it’ll likely to perform better in the winter season. This fragrance will suit you best if you want to attract someone very special. It comes with notes of apricot, Coconut, plum, jasmine, caraway, vanilla, almond and jasmine these sweet and fresh smelling notes will assure you of smelling good throughout the day.</li>
</ol>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://perfumeonline.ca/blogs/blogs/5-best-perfumes-for-mens</id>
    <published>2018-05-12T10:53:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2018-06-02T04:46:33-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://perfumeonline.ca/blogs/blogs/5-best-perfumes-for-mens"/>
    <title>5 Best Perfumes For Men&apos;s</title>
    <author>
      <name>Perfume Online</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h3><strong>From classic brand to modern brands we picked the best scents for men</strong></h3>
<p>Buying colognes for men is not easy because there are hundreds and thousands of perfumes and colognes out there to buy from many different luxury brands, those can make or spoil our personality. and you know that a properly chosen cologne can make your personality and transform your life. So which are Best smelling cologne for men? Let’s find out.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<a href="https://perfumeonline.ca/collections/new-arrivals/products/sauvage" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Sauvage Christian Dior</strong></a> - House of Dior introduced Sauvage in 2015 and it became an instant hit. Sauvage by Christion Dior combined with some of the top fresh notes such as Calabrian Bergamot, lavender, Vetiver, Pepper etc. the nose behind this scent is Francois Demachy. Sauvage is one of the best perfumes for the man because it is a fresh and citrusy scent and the great balance of base and top notes makes it last long in summer days.         </li>
</ol>
<ol start="2">
<li>
<a href="https://perfumeonline.ca/collections/paco-rabanne/products/one-million" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>One Million Paco Rabbane</strong></a> – this golden fragrance was created in 2008 by acclaimed perfumers Olivier Pescheux, Michel Girard and Christophe Raynaud, this fresh but warm combo of citrus fruits, woods and spices have become a true contemporary classic. Combined with featuring blood mandarin, mint and grapefruit, with occasional hints of rose and amber. It has decent power to stay fresh for the day but warm enough for evening.</li>
</ol>
<ol start="3">
<li>
<a href="https://perfumeonline.ca/collections/yves-saint-laurent/products/ysl-la-nuit-de-lhomme-men"><strong>Yves Saint Laurent L'Homme</strong></a> – this scent was introduced in 2009byperfumers Dominique Ropion, Anne Flipo and Pierre Wargnye. This scent is the best for who want a perfume that attracts women's and also if you want to smell good not overpowered than this is the best scent for men's. this features a cardamom head with faint notes of bergamot and lavender that makes it a great scent for dating and by wearing this scent you will receive compliments from everyone.</li>
</ol>
<ol start="4">
<li>
<a href="https://perfumeonline.ca/collections/shop-under-40/products/armaf-club-nuit-intense" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Armaf Club De Nuit Intense</strong></a> – this fragrance was launched in 2012 and nose behind this perfume is Oliver Polge. Club De Nuit intense by Armaf is a masculine scent featuring top notes lemon, Black Currant, Apple, pineapple, bergamot with occasional hints of Vanilla and patchouli. This fragrance has great balance from top notes to base notes that makes it last all day.</li>
</ol>
<ol start="5">
<li start="5">
<a href="https://perfumeonline.ca/collections/versace/products/versace-eros-men" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Eros Versace</strong></a> – this cologne was created by perfumer Aurelien Guichard and launched in 2012. This cologne gives you a refreshment with notes like mint, lemon, Tonka bean, geranium and green apple. The addictive sensual nature of the scent is great for all occasions. This is the cologne for that women raves about.</li>
</ol>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
